https://techindia.com/privacy-policy/

ServicesCardiac Rhythm InterpretationOverviewHolter DiagnosticsCardiac Event / MCT DiagnosticsAmbulatory ECG DiagnosticsCardiac Implant MonitoringSleep Study ReportingE-ICU MonitoringCCM/RPMClinical Trial and ResearchProductsRhythm AIMyBeat CRMCompanyOverviewWhy Us?Our teamThe AcademyWork with usBlogContactHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyYOUR PRIVACY MATTERSThank you for visiting www.techindia.com, which is owned and operated by techindia.com. TechIndia is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully in order to understand what information TechIndia collects about visitors to the Site, and how TechIndia uses that information. If you do not agree with the content of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site. We encourage you to check our Site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions of Use in effect and any changes that may have been made to them. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy we will post the revised Privacy Policy and the revised effective date on this Site. This Policy is part of our Terms and Conditions of Use. Please click here to see that agreement.TechIndia collects two types of information from visitors to the Site, non-personal information and personal information. Non-personal information is information that does not, by itself, identify the visitor as a specific individual. Personal information, is information that identifies a visitor to the Site, or which includes contact information. If you submit a business enquiry to TechIndia, or express interest in the TechIndia Outsourcing service, TechIndia may request personal information from you, including your e-mail address. By providing TechIndia with personal information via the Site, you expressly agree to its collection and use as described in this Privacy Policy. You may obtain access to your personal information collected by TechIndia by sending an e-mail to privacy@techindia.com.On some pages, you may opt to provide us information about yourself if you are interested (a) in serving as an investigator in a clinical trial; or (b) in an employment opportunity at TechIndia; or (c) in having Techindia participate at your event. The information requested from you will be based on your area of interest.On occasion, TechIndia may request that you voluntarily participate in a survey or poll such as feedback on Web site content or services. Your responses will be anonymous unless you opt in to being contacted by email to provide further information regarding the survey.qualified customers or physicians may enter identifying information that allows them to access their TechIndia project & Process information, subscription services, or service offerings.COLLECTION OF INFORMATIONVisitors may access the Site while remaining anonymous and without revealing any personal information. TechIndia may collect information during your visit to the Site through our automatic data collection tools, which may include cookies and other commonly used information-gathering tools. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the website from which you arrived at a TechIndia website. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address and clickstream behavior (i.e. the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with TechIndia websites).A “cookie” is a small piece of data stored on a user’s browser, and contains non-personally identifiable information about the user. When you visit the website, TechIndia may place a “cookie” in order to improve your experience by recognizing you when you visit the website and in order to allow the company to optimize the information presented based on your demonstrated areas of interest. Cookies may also be used to compile information about website usage. If you subsequently provide us with personal information such as your email address, we will associate any cookies on your browser with that information such that you will no longer be an anonymous visitor to the site.CHILDREN’S PRIVACYTechIndia is committed to protecting the privacy of young children, and therefore does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under the age of 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SITE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. In the event that TechIndia discovers that personal information has been collected from a person under 13 years of age, without verified parental consent in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”), TechIndia will delete such information.HOW TECHINDIA USES AND SHARES INFORMATIONTechIndia may use personal information you provide in order to contact you.We store the information you provide about yourself in a secure environment in order to provide you with the information, products, and/or services you request. The information is stored for the lifetime of the system unless you request that it be removed. You must opt-in or give consent for us to share your identifiable information with third parties, who would be bound by a confidentiality agreement. However, the information you provide us about yourself will be shared with TechIndia employees to the extent necessary to accommodate your request.For example, if you provide your name, mailing address, telephone and email address and request more information about TechIndia’s services, this information will be shared with appropriate TechIndia personnel to fulfill your request.Because TechIndia is committed to protecting your privacy, TechIndia will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose this information to any third party, except as described in this Privacy Policy. Personal information may be disclosed under the limited circumstances described below, and you agree that TechIndia may do so by submitting your personal information. By providing any personal information to the Site, all users, including without limitation users, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information within our internal use. TechIndia may share non-personal information from which individuals cannot be identified, and which do not relate to individuals in aggregate form, with third parties for business purposes, such as consultants and advisors to the company. TechIndia will disclose your personal information to a third party if required to do so by law or if, in good faith, TechIndia believes that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend the company’s rights and property or prevent fraud; (3) protect the company against abuse, misuse or unauthorized use of TechIndia’s products or services; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of its personnel, users of this Site or the public. The servers that serve the Site automatically identify a computer by its IP address. If TechIndia, in good faith, determines that you have used the service to menace, threaten, harass, intimidate or otherwise deceptively pose as another person, your actions will be investigated and your IP address may be disclosed to the recipient of any email, their legal counsel or representatives, and law enforcement officials as part of such an investigation. TechIndia may transfer its database, including personal information contained therein, to a third party who acquires all or substantially all of the assets or stock of TechIndia whether by merger, acquisition, reorganization or otherwise.LINKED WEBSITESOur Web site may contain links to other Web sites. You should carefully review the privacy policies and practices of other Web sites, as we cannot control or be responsible for privacy policies or practices of third-party Web sites that are not TechIndia’ Web properties. For links to other TechIndia’ Web properties, please review those privacy terms as well, as they may differ from those on this Web site.NOTIFICATION OF CHANGESAs we provide more services on our Web site and as privacy laws and regulations evolve, it may be necessary to revise or update our Privacy Policy without notice, but we will post those changes on our Web site’s home page so our users are aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. However, we will continue to protect your identifiable information.TECHINDIAS’ GLOBAL PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENTHow To Contact Us : Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send an email to the Council on Data Protection in care of privacy@techindia.comThis privacy policy was last updated on May 12, 2012.SECURITYWe maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction of the personal information you provide on this website. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure.LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITESWe may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These sites may have their own privacy statements in place, which we recommend you review if you visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content of linked sites or any use of the sites.Contact us We're helping some of the most respected names in healthcare deliver measurably better outcomes. Let us show you what personally Human & AI integrated solution can do for your organization. While filling the form, please fill in the information more specifically that you are looking for.Thank you for your query! We will get back to you shortly!!Name *Company NameEmail Address *TelephoneMessage *Submit
